A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
What is this place? Where am I?
Wherever it is, it's completely dark.
I can't even see my own body.
It hurts.
Which way is up? Which way is down?
Where am I supposed to go?
Someone help me.
What? Is that a way out?
No! No, stop!
Voice. Maka. It's Maka's voice.
Wait there! I'm coming!
Saul!
Saul! Saul!
What's the matter?
Good, Dr. Medusa! It's Saul!
Ah!
Saul.
I'm all right.
I'll be okay.
I just had a bad dream, that's all.
That's good, Saul.
But if anything does come up, call me right away.
Ragnarok's black blood is mixed in with Soul Eaters.
It looks like I may have found myself a new research subject.
Listen to me.
He hosts the lyrics.
Let's see that in the air.
I'd love you.
Thank you.
So, I'm...
See...
there you go.
Sweet Quaker!
ok
Super great to see the dialogue here.
Had a secret subcrow telling the audience for a while.
Ted's coming up throughivol faci the fire sestue.
nggak
Do you hear the sounds?
lo-okuninите-muna- Shaun
Yogi sei moakarose
demunyioro ho haji saat
didn't keep the way
that any of you
were
hoping
away
All right, then, Sol.
I'm going to head home.
Unless you need something, are you thirsty?
Do you want me to get you a drink before I go?
No, don't worry about it.
What goes in must come out.
And I'm not too crazy about taking a leak in these stupid bedpans.
Okay.
Do you want me to bring you anything when I come back besides a change of underwear?
Hmm.
Nope, I can't think of anything.
Okay.
Hey, Maka, I'm in this bed because of something I did, not because of you.
So don't get yourself all worked up about it, okay?
Sorry.
Crap.
I think I just made her feel worse.
Way to go, Sol.
I'm an idiot letting my emotions show like that.
It's not going to do any good to get Sol worried about me.
Papa?
Come up to the roof with me.
We can watch the sunset.
Well, I'm here.
What am I supposed to do now?
Clean.
Put the library back in order.
Huh?
No way, not me.
Listen, you brat.
On your last extracurricular lesson, you didn't collect a single soul.
Yeah, well, that's what remedial lessons are for, right?
I should know I've done enough of them lately.
What will stacking books do me?
Cleaning?
No way.
I'm too big for that.
Stars don't clean.
Isn't there anything better for me to do, like when we beat up you and the crazy professor?
Listen up for once, Black Star.
You have more raw power than almost anyone else in your class.
And yet you have nothing to show for it.
It isn't fair to Tsubaki.
She's trying hard and you're holding her back.
Right now, what you need is punishment.
Something tedious and boring to get you back on track.
This is a huge mess.
Aren't you at least going to help me?
That would defeat the purpose.
I don't spoil my students.
That's not the kind of man I was.
Great.
What am I going to do now?
Charisma Justice is awesome.
He's almost as big a star as I am.
I never knew they had comic books in the library.
This is the kind of remedial lesson that I can live with.
Hey, keep it down, would you?
You're in a library.
Yeah, sorry.
What are you doing here, kid?
Are you being punished, too?
No, I'm here to check out a book.
I'm conducting some research into the symmetry of famous weapons.
I'd actually like to take that book that's under your butt,
if you don't mind moving for a second.
Oh, right here?
What does the cover say?
E-ex-calibur?
Almost. Excalibur.
Yeah, what's that?
From what I've heard, it's a legendary weapon,
also known as the Holy Sword.
They say he who draws the Holy Sword from the ground
will be deemed a hero
and shall receive everlasting glory and fame.
I've heard that someone who obtained Excalibur in the past
went on to become a mighty king.
I'll bet a sword as powerful as this one
has absolutely flawless symmetry.
Oh, symmetry.
Hero?
King?
That sounds perfect to me.
Oh, you mean Excalibur, huh?
Hey, Professor.
Are you here for punishment, too?
Punishment?
What are you talking about, Black Star?
Do you know anything about the Legend of Excalibur?
The Holy Sword Excalibur.
It was too much even for me.
Really?
You tried to pull the sword?
Even you couldn't draw the sword, Professor?
The Holy Sword Excalibur.
Now I'm really interested.
Legend of the Holy Sword.
Kid and Black Star's great adventure?
Look at that marker.
You see how ridiculous the sun looks
trying to fight off sleep?
Pretty funny.
This isn't going well at all.
I finally have a chance to talk to Maka,
and I don't have a clue what to talk about.
The way the sun looks is a pretty lame topic.
She pulled out a book.
She's bored with me.
I have to say something quick.
Something cleverer, something funny.
Think, think.
Think faster, idiot.
Hey, you shouldn't be reading in this light.
It's bad for your eyes.
Really?
Did I just start off by lecturing her?
Hey, Papa.
How do you feel about Mama?
Be honest.
Don't show any hesitation.
That's easy.
I love her, of course.
Then how come you cheated on her all the time?
That was way too much hesitation.
Now, no matter what I say, it looks out convincing.
I'm in big trouble.
Hang in there.
Millions of men everywhere are on your side.
Don't run away from this.
Stand and face your daughter like a man.
Don't run.
It's getting chilly, don't you think?
Maybe we should head inside, huh?
Already?
But we just got here.
I didn't run away quick enough!
All these pointed questions.
She's starting to take after her mother.
Listen, Maka.
Papa loves you and Mama more than anything in the world.
And that's the truth.
That's the truth.
It is the truth.
I swear it's the truth, Maka!
This is it.
Yahoo!
Excalibur's up there waiting for me.
Yes.
According to this, we'll have to climb up there and find the cave the sword is in.
Hey!
Not there!
Dammit!
Squirled rich kids have all the best toys, don't they?
You're not leaving me behind!
Kid's not here.
Where'd he go?
In there, maybe?
Black Star?
Huh?
I can't come down.
There's water.
My pants are going to get wet.
What are you talking about?
You carry me.
Yeah, right.
You can stay there.
Such a terrible obstacle so early in the quest.
Our chosen path is truly a cruel one.
Yeah, you've really got it rough here, don't you?
I'll ward off the water from above and you can handle the water on the ground, okay?
We'll work together.
It's a good thing there are two of us here.
This way would be impassable alone.
Quite an obstacle.
Dude, you're kind of a useless idiot, aren't you?
It looks like a fairy.
What's something like that doing here?
We're hunting after a legendary sword.
Finding a fairy or two shouldn't be surprising.
Is Excalibur up ahead?
Are we in the right place?
She's not a very polite fairy, is she?
Looks like the path dead ends here.
Hey, over there.
Yes, no doubt about it.
That's it.
The Holy Sword Excalibur.
Awesome.
The air here is vibrating.
Standing here, I can easily believe what the book says about becoming a hero and earning everlasting fame and glory.
This cave certainly seems like a magical place.
Just look at the sword.
Such precise, detailed ornamentation on the hilt and not a single nick on the blade.
This is indeed deserving of the title Holy Sword.
A magnificent sword which can only be pulled out by the chosen hero.
By me.
Yeah, looks like I'm a hero.
No, it can't be.
This is some kind of mistake.
I hate to break it to you, but you're no hero.
How about a do-over?
Huh?
You saying that didn't count or something?
Fine, but I'm sure it's just going to be the same every time.
No, this time I'm going to do it.
Yeah, right, you wish.
The sword chose me to be its hero, kid.
I'm a big, fat hero.
Best to be safe.
Who knows who else has touched this sword over the years.
Hurry up and do it.
It came out, huh?
How come you were able to get it out, too?
It must be because I loosened it.
Welcome.
Welcome to my cave, young ones.
It's talking.
Please forgive the belated salutations.
I am the holy sword, Excalibur.
How incredibly...
Lame!
Papa, would you tell me more about the demon sword, Ragnarok?
Long ago, Meisters and Weapons worked together under Lord Death to maintain peace and order in the world,
the same function for which you are being trained.
No Meister and Weapon pair was allowed to collect the soul of a human being for any reason whatsoever.
That rule still stands, and now it seems as natural to us as breathing.
Because while a human soul increases a weapon's ability and power, just as a Kishan soul does, the price is steep.
A weapon that takes a human soul will pay by losing his or her own human heart.
Despite the risk, however, there were Meisters who broke that sacred rule.
These Meisters feared death above all else.
Their constant battles left them frightened, broken, and they took to hunting human souls.
Again and again, they defied the rule, secretly feeding their weapons the souls of innocent humans.
As a result, a Kishan was born into this world.
Death Weapon Meister Academy was founded in order to recover souls who have left the human path and become eggs of Kishan.
It was also created to train and oversee Meisters and Weapons who are too young to hunt down evil without someone to guide them.
The ultimate goal is to prevent the Kishan from ever being reborn and once again raining terror down upon the world.
So, the demon sword...
Yes. It devours human souls.
It was melted down by a witch and implanted in the body of a Meister as black blood.
Now, the demon sword, Ragnarok, is only one step away from becoming a Kishan.
And it's not just the sword we have to worry about.
There are people who could become Kishan as well.
And beyond that, there's Soul, whose body now contains black blood.
Let's see. Are you still hard at work like a good boy black star?
Ooh, see what you can do if you put your mind to it?
Oh, hi, Professor Sid. After I put this book away, I'll be all done.
Tsubaki? So that sneaky little brat dumped his punishment on her and took off, did he?
Back when I was still alive, I hated it when dirty tricks like this were pulled.
It's okay, Professor. Don't worry about it. I enjoy cleaning.
If you're looking for black star, he's not here. He and Kid went to find the holy sword.
Why, has he done something wrong?
The holy sword?
Yes. Excalibur.
The same sword that tears the air and shakes the very ground?
Let's stop talking about it.
Yeah. In some way, this is the ultimate remedial lesson.
I'll let this one slide. That's the kind of man I was.
Okay. I've got a bunch of tests that need greeting.
You're the holy sword? In the top hat? Seriously?
You're one to talk in that funny outfit. Who are you exactly?
Who am I? I'm Blackstar!
My legend dates back to the 12th century, thank you very much.
From the looks of you, you must be meisters. Where are your children from?
Who do you think you are pointing that thing at me? Put it down, freak!
We're from death, we're in mine. I know that. Here, I want to show you something.
Then why did you ask if you already knew the answer?
What's with this guy? Why the hell isn't he wearing any pants?
What's he showing us, I wonder?
Young ones, do you want to hear the legend of me?
Put that thing away!
Do you want to hear a heroic tale?
Get that out of my face!
Where have you traveled here from?
Like we said, we're from Death Weapon Meister.
What is your favorite number between 1 and 12?
What? Between 1 and 12?
1, obviously, because I refuse to back down until I'm number 1.
And mine is 8 because of its perfect symmetry.
Hools! What right do you have to choose a number?
My legend dates all the way back to the 12th century, you know.
You asked us to pick a favorite number, so we did.
Do you want to hear my legend or not?
Just quit with the cane already, will ya?
As I said, my legend begins in the 12th century.
My mornings begin with a cup of coffee with cream at the cafe.
My afternoons begin with a cup of hot tea with two lumps of sugar.
And my evenings...
Let me guess, booze.
Sounds right for an old guy like you.
In the evening, I change into my pajamas.
Why do we care about that?
That's all irrelevant to the legend.
The seven ages.
Do you know what this hat is?
Huh?
I asked, do you know what this hat is?
How should we know that?
It appears to be made of silk, if that's what you mean.
Fools!
If you don't know, I guess I'll have to tell you.
The taller the chef's hat, the greater the chef.
Okay, so what you're trying to tell us then...
Who said that I was a chef?
Dude, nothing you're saying makes any sense.
This is why I can't abide hayseeds.
You're beyond annoying!
Blackstar, calm down.
Don't let this guy and his nonsense get to you.
Holy sword, you gotta be kidding me!
Let me see that book!
It's completely unreliable!
Who wrote this?
Let's see.
The author is...
E. Excalibur?
Excalibur.
It was you!
No autographs.
Professor, I have a question.
What kind of weapon is the holy sword?
Oh.
That, huh?
Whoever draws the sword is said to be made a great king, given wings of light and granted
the ability to soar through the sky.
The sword can cut through space with a single swing.
Without a doubt, it is the most powerful weapon in the world.
I see.
But only a hero who's been chosen can match soul wavelengths with it, right?
Hmm.
No.
That's not true, unfortunately.
Surprisingly enough, Excalibur can match with anyone.
Before becoming my Meister, there is a list of a thousand provisions you must peruse.
Be sure to look through all of them.
They're important.
Even the backs of these pages have been written on.
I greatly look forward to your participation in number 452, the five-hour storytelling party.
And thus...
Thus you have been chosen.
It shall all be yours.
Victory and glory.
Victory.
Glory.
Now let's go.
Together.
Yeah, right.
Who'd ever want a sword like you?
Useless piece of metal.
Anybody can match their soul wavelength with the sword just fine.
But there's no one in the world who can ever match personal wavelengths with Excalibur.
Babe.
Hold on.
Come back.
I tell you what.
I can lower those 1,000 provisions down to 800.
Just as long as you take part in this storytelling party.
Anyone who can put up with him is a hero.
Disgusting.
Oh, hi.
Did you meet the Holy Sword Excalibur?
Yeah, they met him.
We've both got fine partners already, huh?
Hmm?
All right.
It looks like the gang is all here.
Hey, So.
So, are you all fixed up now?
The real party can't get started without you around.
Yeah.
I'm a lot better.
Do you hear that, Black Star?
I'm starting to get the strange feeling that other people have been laughing at us.
Huh?
Those two?
They're the ones?
Yeah, it's for them.
Hey, Black Star.
Kid, come here.
I think you better see this.
Hmm?
Is he serious?
What is that thing?
Don't know.
It's intense.
That freak!
Disgusting.
Huh?
Not a dream or not.
Oh,?
What does it need for me to score?
Oh, man.
How about it?
Oh, but I dunno.
Yeah.
How about it?
Oh, man.
I'd rather the leap.
I'd rather the leap go.
The leap of the leap.
See you next time.
I love it!
In the next episode of Soul Eater, the enchanted sword Masamune, rake the soul possession.
A heart sings in the rain?
Fool!
You're so annoying!